<rdf:RDF
    xmlns:spdx="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:doap="http://usefulinc.com/ns/doap#"
    xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#">
  <spdx:SpdxNoAssertionLicense rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#NOASSERTION_LICENSE_ID"/>
  <spdx:SpdxDocument rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-DOCUMENT">
    <spdx:creationInfo>
      <spdx:CreationInfo>
        <rdfs:comment>This document was created using license information and a generator from Fossology.
The scanner findings were reviewed and confirmed resp. corrected by Oliver Fendt</rdfs:comment>
        <spdx:created>2022-03-22T15:07:56Z</spdx:created>
        <spdx:creator>Person: Oliver Fendt</spdx:creator>
        <spdx:creator>Tool: spdx2</spdx:creator>
        <spdx:licenseListVersion>2.6</spdx:licenseListVersion>
      </spdx:CreationInfo>
    </spdx:creationInfo>
    <spdx:relationship>
      <spdx:Relationship>
        <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
          <spdx:Package rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-upload7">
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183436">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>3514b3811feb5c47e46179347821bc22b898cb32a59b76c8917a9db1718c7a81</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>b3d42f35953fdfd55b0350aac1d97e2c</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>4a54ad13cfd818ad327a309f1facbd0af7bc54d5</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/README.md</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:packageFileName>clock-1.1.0.zip</spdx:packageFileName>
            <spdx:licenseDeclared rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183437">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>In the file the following is written:
"All files in the project must start with the following header.

    // Copyright (c) 2017, the Dart project authors.  Please see the AUTHORS file
    // for details. All rights reserved. Use of this source code is governed by a
    // BSD-style license that can be found in the LICENSE file."

This is an element of the project governance, requiring the above mentioned license reference header in every new file. It is not the licensing of this file and is in the context of the concrete licensing irrelevant, this applies also to the required signed CLAs and CCLAs mentioned in this file.</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>156ba15d1a3f53833808dbc6065f2ad351fb6131ad9f4709b3b4af3a212439c2</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>6befa3539b648b5446cb046359a440dd</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>003b12dae85d1b5f25e70247412eae35c9ef4dd6</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-BSD">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-BSD</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:extractedText>BSD is referenced without a version number. Please look up BSD in the License Admin to view the different versions.</spdx:extractedText>
                        <spdx:name>BSD</spdx:name>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/CONTRIBUTING.md</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183421">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e73dfb40a24474e3b0e3d4ca78b9940306aff3f0</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8357ae87eeecf684dc90c1b01398fa4ff00cf7bd13b07bdbe921dd7910be199d</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8048cf3dd9a6092d4cc3e94d956c1e58</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-Apache-2.0</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:extractedText>Apache License

Version 2.0, January 2004

http://www.apache.org/licenses/ TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION

   1. Definitions.

      

      "License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

      

      "Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.

      

      "Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, "control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

      

      "You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License.

      

      "Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files.

      

      "Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.

      

      "Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below).

      

      "Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

      

      "Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted" means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."

      

      "Contributor" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.

   2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

   3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed.

   4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions:

      (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and

      (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and

      (c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and

      (d) If the Work includes a "NOTICE" text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.

      You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License.

   5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

   6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

   7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

   8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

   9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability. END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.

To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "[]" replaced with your own identifying information. (Don't include the brackets!) The text should be enclosed in the appropriate comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a file or class name and description of purpose be included on the same "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier identification within third-party archives.

Copyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner]

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");

you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.

You may obtain a copy of the License at

http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software

distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,

WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.

See the License for the specific language governing permissions and

limitations under the License.</spdx:extractedText>
                        <spdx:name>Apache License 2.0</spdx:name>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseConcluded>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/test/stopwatch_test.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183428">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2013 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ae0a4ab874ab1aa0eefd1efc0c02bbdc1c19729d</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>51ebcd269b659d6f789f8858b98a287b1a8fed65d852fe6e748ff75e81e56cba</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>2c91507ecca892cf65c6eaf3fbe0a7e6</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/lib/clock.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183426">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>197c919dd4e5000d37db54e4163a1574</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>bac19a57eabddc8de0acf7e29132b127872f9b4f</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>384bb4bf19d1c3bacefed0e62642a9377c4ef8544205519533aca34e3fa7bac9</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/.github/workflows/test-package.yml</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183438">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>16d2b365bbac37dc10ace74318886990</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7fd1175cfef9255b9b18c35b4b1b7edfee6ade74c70a2a3fe510e0d77b8e787a</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>5353265dcff51bae27548dad8d282779a307ebd9</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/pubspec.yaml</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:name>clock-1.1.0.zip</spdx:name>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183440">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>32e7b19f0ab2d21ac50f77a6bd1b6428acec936c</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>27a763e6fee2148bcb996854f665e17de1744026eb7cb12a012d5cae20b32823</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>2c5f68ccfa5b74183cb4c136de07c20e</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/CHANGELOG.md</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:licenseInfoFromFiles rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183419">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2013 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>a6f9e9098ec779e0b76620fbb673f0a9</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>55aa074a223ec05624f152e14c156122d757c9d4</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>b049df812a2e3bf32e7043b61476f1f8d22ba082ad50aba810dd5c8db8f86160</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/test/clock_test.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183433">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f116a9022428d7c99b87c7d9caa25d1599ec416856b0ecd69e92ec161074782c</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e85b4f3cf370581b3ef11497a9a5bce3</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>741146996f0af70299db342f86ada3581f49df3e</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/lib/src/utils.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183430">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>89cccc8fd436a87583afaf028b7b2b5b8c9164f4</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>11ad3f87e1b2c80aa52bf25b8396a3168f84d9939e0c8b2cbde1c3ae72013b7a</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>46e3039b7f99a958f8cca0ecb6743b06</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/lib/src/default.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183434">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f58126ba1c097466967caf5580adbad1</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>6e53de5941db5b904a91e5dfca92cbbb93b21b5a</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>9c6b0e87edbec588028e586d1a45727662cb0e4b353e372c86fac0c38bdcba4b</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/.gitignore</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:checksum>
              <spdx:Checksum>
                <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                <spdx:checksumValue>99cd3758c8f62ab8bfd275e9df4ac8f9</spdx:checksumValue>
              </spdx:Checksum>
            </spdx:checksum>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183423">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>1128f8f91104ba9ef98d37eea6523a888dcfa5de</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>58d1e17ffe5109a7ae296caafcadfdbe6a7d176f0bc4ab01e12a689b0499d8bd</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>175792518e4ac015ab6696d16c4f607e</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/LICENSE</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183435">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>004a85f70a68f46a1b65ecd31422b1a1</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>48c18212868b7c3943756ce5c53a8f931f82921f</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>85337aeeee55c79d4a1da86d1393354c14e4a5f0daf402de66ffe974c51694bf</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/AUTHORS</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183439">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>4e71b3ddf2f5b525f79bd6e4c3d5b665cc02574c</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>54c620d0ad09f4e047ead16971e54958b2a0c064d9513e8189df86da7066e396</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>fa628bc05d35713682bbd17b2033e397</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/analysis_options.yaml</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183432">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f3c8ef41609f89616aa27c4449b67b4f8e17e0112aad154ff4564a35bcedd090</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f38a99a51f4062e7861bb366f85265d5</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>5a36925abbeae52ffb4c9f00b15f021aefc19d71</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/lib/src/stopwatch.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183422">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>648a9d0f8fbe1af5e7af255ca493e8cf4f499225</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>4e20d309bf526a070dc04e5f0fe2b4d9d2dfd2a1709d6feed44083b27416bbda</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>70b171ffaeb5543ea20c197d896f1c9c</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/test/utils.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:packageVerificationCode>
              <spdx:PackageVerificationCode>
                <spdx:packageVerificationCodeValue>50d87bcd2d48a718c1168a02240070d87ccc6d38</spdx:packageVerificationCodeValue>
              </spdx:PackageVerificationCode>
            </spdx:packageVerificationCode>
            <spdx:checksum>
              <spdx:Checksum>
                <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                <spdx:checksumValue>b097a30488519558be63335f1b9b62621cda58f2</spdx:checksumValue>
              </spdx:Checksum>
            </spdx:checksum>
            <spdx:checksum>
              <spdx:Checksum>
                <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                <spdx:checksumValue>3ed4f876ab7ee9ff7d38936c23b1e727379b0963028edc878285eea44ec692cd</spdx:checksumValue>
              </spdx:Checksum>
            </spdx:checksum>
            <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
            <spdx:licenseComments>licenseInfoInFile determined by Scanners:
 - nomos ("unknown".1cfbe7)
 - monk ("unknown".1cfbe7)
- ojo ("unknown".1cfbe7)</spdx:licenseComments>
            <spdx:downloadLocation>NOASSERTION</spdx:downloadLocation>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183420">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>53ac7ed41b794f041204b23e13eadcfe</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f062dbd90d6fa3a0a62a6b947ab058fa97c4e298</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>de7fae1058e9f15b9e99df5247754a857dbbc2c27e0a44a878452072bcb14eb3</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/test/default_test.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#SPDXRef-item150183431">
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright 2018 Google Inc. All Rights Reserved.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>NOASSERTION</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>1355e7c034fb490a3da4b604bf4a245e</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>a7543f8100c03250b89e5f8e2ce0db6d76eb80c35a71385a2867bd4320ddeb16</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>d68e216c44bd3fb4db58d92831c7dd63d07c64b2</spdx:checksumValue>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>clock-1.1.0.zip/clock-1.1.0/lib/src/clock.dart</spdx:fileName>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
          </spdx:Package>
        </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
        <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_describes"/>
      </spdx:Relationship>
    </spdx:relationship>
    <spdx:name>/srv/fossology/repository/report</spdx:name>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-BSD"/>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo>
      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-No_license_found">
        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-No_license_found</spdx:licenseId>
        <spdx:extractedText>Not find any license in the scanned file</spdx:extractedText>
        <spdx:name>No_license_found</spdx:name>
      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
    </spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://356501fde679/repo/SPDX2TV_clock-1.1.0.zip_1647959150.spdx#LicenseRef-Apache-2.0"/>
    <spdx:specVersion>SPDX-2.2</spdx:specVersion>
    <spdx:dataLicense>
      <spdx:ListedLicense rdf:about="http://spdx.org/licenses/CC0-1.0">
        <spdx:isOsiApproved rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
        >false</spdx:isOsiApproved>
        <spdx:isFsfLibre rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
        >true</spdx:isFsfLibre>
        <spdx:standardLicenseTemplate>&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt;Creative Commons&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt; Legal Code&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;

&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;

CC0 1.0 Universal

&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt; CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION ON AN "AS-IS" BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER.

&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;

Statement of Purpose

The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an "owner") of an original work of authorship and/or a database (each, a "Work").

Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for the purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and scientific works ("Commons") that the public can reliably and without fear of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other works, reuse and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever and for any purposes, including without limitation commercial purposes. These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific works, or to gain reputation or greater distribution for their Work in part through the use and efforts of others.

For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any expectation of additional consideration or compensation, the person associating CC0 with a Work (the "Affirmer"), to the extent that he or she is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily elects to apply CC0 to the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and Related Rights in the Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.

   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="1.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights ("Copyright and Related Rights"). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not limited to, the following:

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="i.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display, communicate, and translate a Work;

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="ii.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="iii.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person's image or likeness depicted in a Work;

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="iv.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work, subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(a), below;

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="v.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data in a Work;

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="vi.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal protection of databases, and under any national implementation thereof, including any amended or successor version of such directive); and

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="vii.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the world based on applicable law or treaty, and any national implementations thereof.

   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="2.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention of, applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently, irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and causes of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as future claims and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the "Waiver"). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each member of the public at large and to the detriment of Affirmer's heirs and successors, fully intending that such Waiver shall not be subject to revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other legal or equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public as contemplated by Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.

   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="3.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into account Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected person a royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive, irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the "License"). The License shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of the License for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder of the License, and in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she will not (i) exercise any of his or her remaining Copyright and Related Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and causes of action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.

   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="4.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Limitations and Disclaimers.

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="a.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned, surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="b.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or warranties of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including without limitation warranties of title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or the present or absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to the greatest extent permissible under applicable law.

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="c.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without limitation any person's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work. Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the Work.

      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="d.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to this CC0 or use of the Work.&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt; &lt;&lt;var;name="upstreamLink";original="";match="For more information, please see &lt;http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/&gt;"&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;</spdx:standardLicenseTemplate>
        <spdx:licenseTextHtml>
      &lt;div class="optional-license-text"&gt; 
         &lt;div class="optional-license-text"&gt; 
            &lt;p&gt;Creative Commons&lt;var class="optional-license-text"&gt;  Legal Code&lt;/var&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

         &lt;/div&gt;
         &lt;p&gt;CC0 1.0 Universal&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class="optional-license-text"&gt; 
         &lt;p&gt;CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS
         DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION
         ON AN &amp;quot;AS-IS&amp;quot; BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT
         OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM THE
         USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Statement of Purpose&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer exclusive Copyright and Related
         Rights (defined below) upon the creator and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an &amp;quot;owner&amp;quot;)
         of an original work of authorship and/or a database (each, a &amp;quot;Work&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for the purpose of contributing to a
         commons of creative, cultural and scientific works (&amp;quot;Commons&amp;quot;) that the public can reliably
         and without fear of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other works, reuse
         and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever and for any purposes, including without
         limitation commercial purposes. These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a
         free culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific works, or to gain
         reputation or greater distribution for their Work in part through the use and efforts of others.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any expectation of additional consideration
         or compensation, the person associating CC0 with a Work (the &amp;quot;Affirmer&amp;quot;), to the extent that
         he or she is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily elects to apply CC0 to
         the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and
         Related Rights in the Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul style="list-style:none"&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; 1.&lt;/var&gt;
          Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be protected by copyright and
             related or neighboring rights (&amp;quot;Copyright and Related Rights&amp;quot;). Copyright and
             Related Rights include, but are not limited to, the following:
          
&lt;ul style="list-style:none"&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; i.&lt;/var&gt;
              the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display, communicate, and translate a Work;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; ii.&lt;/var&gt;
              moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; iii.&lt;/var&gt;
              publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person&amp;apos;s image or likeness depicted in a Work;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; iv.&lt;/var&gt;
              rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work, subject to the limitations
                 in paragraph 4(a), below;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; v.&lt;/var&gt;
              rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data in a Work;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; vi.&lt;/var&gt;
              database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the European Parliament and
                 of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal protection of databases, and under any
                 national implementation thereof, including any amended or successor version of such
                 directive); and
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; vii.&lt;/var&gt;
              other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the world based on applicable
                 law or treaty, and any national implementations thereof.
            &lt;/li&gt;
            
&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; 2.&lt;/var&gt;
          Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention of, applicable law,
             Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently, irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons,
             and surrenders all of Affirmer&amp;apos;s Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and
             causes of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as future claims
             and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum
             duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any
             current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever,
             including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the
             &amp;quot;Waiver&amp;quot;). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each member of the public at
             large and to the detriment of Affirmer&amp;apos;s heirs and successors, fully intending that such
             Waiver shall not be subject to revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other
             legal or equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public as
             contemplated by Affirmer&amp;apos;s express Statement of Purpose.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; 3.&lt;/var&gt;
          Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason be judged legally invalid
             or ineffective under applicable law, then the Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent
             permitted taking into account Affirmer&amp;apos;s express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to
             the extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected person a
             royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive, irrevocable and
             unconditional license to exercise Affirmer&amp;apos;s Copyright and Related Rights in the Work (i)
             in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or
             treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any
             number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation
             commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the &amp;quot;License&amp;quot;). The License shall
             be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of
             the License for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such
             partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder of the License, and
             in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she will not (i) exercise any of his or her
             remaining Copyright and Related Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and
             causes of action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer&amp;apos;s express
             Statement of Purpose.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; 4.&lt;/var&gt;
          Limitations and Disclaimers.
          
&lt;ul style="list-style:none"&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; a.&lt;/var&gt;
              No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned, surrendered, licensed
                 or otherwise affected by this document.
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; b.&lt;/var&gt;
              Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or warranties of any kind
                 concerning the Work, express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including without
                 limitation warranties of title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non
                 infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or the present or
                 absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to the greatest extent permissible
                 under applicable law.
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; c.&lt;/var&gt;
              Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons that may apply to the
                 Work or any use thereof, including without limitation any person&amp;apos;s Copyright and
                 Related Rights in the Work. Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any
                 necessary consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the Work.
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; d.&lt;/var&gt;
              Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a party to this document
                 and has no duty or obligation with respect to this CC0 or use of the Work.
            &lt;/li&gt;
            
&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
      
&lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;var class="optional-license-text"&gt; &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt; &lt;/var&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
    </spdx:licenseTextHtml>
        <spdx:isDeprecatedLicenseId rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
        >false</spdx:isDeprecatedLicenseId>
        <spdx:name>Creative Commons Zero v1.0 Universal</spdx:name>
        <spdx:crossRef>
          <spdx:CrossRef>
            <spdx:order rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#int"
            >0</spdx:order>
            <spdx:timestamp>2023-06-18T16:40:19Z</spdx:timestamp>
            <spdx:url>https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/legalcode</spdx:url>
            <spdx:match>false</spdx:match>
            <spdx:isWayBackLink rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >false</spdx:isWayBackLink>
            <spdx:isValid rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >true</spdx:isValid>
            <spdx:isLive rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >true</spdx:isLive>
          </spdx:CrossRef>
        </spdx:crossRef>
        <spdx:licenseId>CC0-1.0</spdx:licenseId>
        <spdx:licenseText>Creative Commons Legal Code

CC0 1.0 Universal

    CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE
    LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN
    ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS
    INFORMATION ON AN "AS-IS" BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES
    REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS
    PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM
    THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED
    HEREUNDER.

Statement of Purpose

The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer
exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator
and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an "owner") of an original work of
authorship and/or a database (each, a "Work").

Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for
the purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and
scientific works ("Commons") that the public can reliably and without fear
of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other
works, reuse and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever
and for any purposes, including without limitation commercial purposes.
These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free
culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific
works, or to gain reputation or greater distribution for their Work in
part through the use and efforts of others.

For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any
expectation of additional consideration or compensation, the person
associating CC0 with a Work (the "Affirmer"), to the extent that he or she
is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily
elects to apply CC0 to the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its
terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and Related Rights in the
Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.

1. Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be
protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights ("Copyright and
Related Rights"). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not
limited to, the following:

  i. the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display,
     communicate, and translate a Work;
 ii. moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
iii. publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person's image or
     likeness depicted in a Work;
 iv. rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work,
     subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(a), below;
  v. rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data
     in a Work;
 vi. database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the
     European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal
     protection of databases, and under any national implementation
     thereof, including any amended or successor version of such
     directive); and
vii. other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the
     world based on applicable law or treaty, and any national
     implementations thereof.

2. Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention
of, applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently,
irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of
Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and causes
of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as
future claims and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories
worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or
treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future
medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever,
including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional
purposes (the "Waiver"). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each
member of the public at large and to the detriment of Affirmer's heirs and
successors, fully intending that such Waiver shall not be subject to
revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other legal or
equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public
as contemplated by Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.

3. Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason
be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the
Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into
account Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the
extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected
person a royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive,
irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise Affirmer's Copyright and
Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the
maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future
time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number
of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without
limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the
"License"). The License shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was
applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of the License for any
reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such
partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder
of the License, and in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she
will not (i) exercise any of his or her remaining Copyright and Related
Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and causes of
action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer's
express Statement of Purpose.

4. Limitations and Disclaimers.

 a. No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned,
    surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.
 b. Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or
    warranties of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied,
    statutory or otherwise, including without limitation warranties of
    title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non
    infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or
    the present or absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to
    the greatest extent permissible under applicable law.
 c. Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons
    that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without
    limitation any person's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work.
    Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary
    consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the
    Work.
 d. Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a
    party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to
    this CC0 or use of the Work.
</spdx:licenseText>
        <rdfs:seeAlso>https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/legalcode</rdfs:seeAlso>
      </spdx:ListedLicense>
    </spdx:dataLicense>
  </spdx:SpdxDocument>
</rdf:RDF>
