<rdf:RDF
    xmlns:spdx="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:doap="http://usefulinc.com/ns/doap#"
    xmlns:ptr="http://www.w3.org/2009/pointers#"
    xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#">
  <spdx:SpdxDocument rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-DOCUMENT">
    <spdx:relationship>
      <spdx:Relationship>
        <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_describes"/>
        <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
          <spdx:Package rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-upload2172">
            <spdx:downloadLocation>https://files.pythonhosted.org/packages/40/fc/914289fdaf33352ab3412fc1fdc96c4c902715601bc603859bc533b51f5c/adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip</spdx:downloadLocation>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576938">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/adodbapi.egg-info/not-zip-safe</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ba8ab5a0280b953aa97435ff8946cbcbb2755a27</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7eb70257593da06f682a3ddda54a9d260d4fc514f645237f5ca74b08f8da61a6</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>81051bcc2cf1bedf378224b0a93e2877</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576931">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/process_connect_string.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>a1653e9e1e70b541ad7ac6d3bc4741f3883ccb7a392e5d418c978283cdcd2127</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>088332a9239fea53a889f3c6891956f7</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>352922f6d420c190a468d75b01ebc834b542c62c</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576920">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/adodbapitestconfig.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>22eccd1024c24cb2c1514821b0fa583fb585b44f579d41df62cdea2f2206f5eb</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>48a9aff494b5f4eec80ee8613a231796</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c1e0a0affb0784982564e8d0ec5fad7dec64a144</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:licenseInfoFromFiles rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576901">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-LGPL</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>GNU Lesser General Public License</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>LGPL is referenced without a version number. Please look up LGPL in the License Admin to view the different versions.</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.0-or-later">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-LGPL-2.0-or-later</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>GNU Library General Public License v2 or later</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>GNU LIBRARY GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE

Version 2, June 1991

Copyright (C) 1991 Free Software Foundation, Inc.

51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA

Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.

[This is the first released version of the library GPL. It is numbered 2 because it goes with version 2 of the ordinary GPL.]

Preamble

The licenses for most software are designed to take away your freedom to share and change it. By contrast, the GNU General Public Licenses are intended to guarantee your freedom to share and change free software--to make sure the software is free for all its users.

This license, the Library General Public License, applies to some specially designated Free Software Foundation software, and to any other libraries whose authors decide to use it. You can use it for your libraries, too.

When we speak of free software, we are referring to freedom, not price. Our General Public Licenses are designed to make sure that you have the freedom to distribute copies of free software (and charge for this service if you wish), that you receive source code or can get it if you want it, that you can change the software or use pieces of it in new free programs; and that you know you can do these things.

To protect your rights, we need to make restrictions that forbid anyone to deny you these rights or to ask you to surrender the rights. These restrictions translate to certain responsibilities for you if you distribute copies of the library, or if you modify it.

For example, if you distribute copies of the library, whether gratis or for a fee, you must give the recipients all the rights that we gave you. You must make sure that they, too, receive or can get the source code. If you link a program with the library, you must provide complete object files to the recipients so that they can relink them with the library, after making changes to the library and recompiling it. And you must show them these terms so they know their rights.

Our method of protecting your rights has two steps: (1) copyright the library, and (2) offer you this license which gives you legal permission to copy, distribute and/or modify the library.

Also, for each distributor's protection, we want to make certain that everyone understands that there is no warranty for this free library. If the library is modified by someone else and passed on, we want its recipients to know that what they have is not the original version, so that any problems introduced by others will not reflect on the original authors' reputations.

Finally, any free program is threatened constantly by software patents. We wish to avoid the danger that companies distributing free software will individually obtain patent licenses, thus in effect transforming the program into proprietary software. To prevent this, we have made it clear that any patent must be licensed for everyone's free use or not licensed at all.

Most GNU software, including some libraries, is covered by the ordinary GNU General Public License, which was designed for utility programs. This license, the GNU Library General Public License, applies to certain designated libraries. This license is quite different from the ordinary one; be sure to read it in full, and don't assume that anything in it is the same as in the ordinary license.

The reason we have a separate public license for some libraries is that they blur the distinction we usually make between modifying or adding to a program and simply using it. Linking a program with a library, without changing the library, is in some sense simply using the library, and is analogous to running a utility program or application program. However, in a textual and legal sense, the linked executable is a combined work, a derivative of the original library, and the ordinary General Public License treats it as such.

Because of this blurred distinction, using the ordinary General Public License for libraries did not effectively promote software sharing, because most developers did not use the libraries. We concluded that weaker conditions might promote sharing better.

However, unrestricted linking of non-free programs would deprive the users of those programs of all benefit from the free status of the libraries themselves. This Library General Public License is intended to permit developers of non-free programs to use free libraries, while preserving your freedom as a user of such programs to change the free libraries that are incorporated in them. (We have not seen how to achieve this as regards changes in header files, but we have achieved it as regards changes in the actual functions of the Library.) The hope is that this will lead to faster development of free libraries.

The precise terms and conditions for copying, distribution and modification follow. Pay close attention to the difference between a "work based on the library" and a "work that uses the library". The former contains code derived from the library, while the latter only works together with the library.

Note that it is possible for a library to be covered by the ordinary General Public License rather than by this special one.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR COPYING, DISTRIBUTION AND MODIFICATION

   0. This License Agreement applies to any software library which contains a notice placed by the copyright holder or other authorized party saying it may be distributed under the terms of this Library General Public License (also called "this License"). Each licensee is addressed as "you".

   A "library" means a collection of software functions and/or data prepared so as to be conveniently linked with application programs (which use some of those functions and data) to form executables.

   The "Library", below, refers to any such software library or work which has been distributed under these terms. A "work based on the Library" means either the Library or any derivative work under copyright law: that is to say, a work containing the Library or a portion of it, either verbatim or with modifications and/or translated straightforwardly into another language. (Hereinafter, translation is included without limitation in the term "modification".)

   "Source code" for a work means the preferred form of the work for making modifications to it. For a library, complete source code means all the source code for all modules it contains, plus any associated interface definition files, plus the scripts used to control compilation and installation of the library.

   Activities other than copying, distribution and modification are not covered by this License; they are outside its scope. The act of running a program using the Library is not restricted, and output from such a program is covered only if its contents constitute a work based on the Library (independent of the use of the Library in a tool for writing it). Whether that is true depends on what the Library does and what the program that uses the Library does.

   1. You may copy and distribute verbatim copies of the Library's complete source code as you receive it, in any medium, provided that you conspicuously and appropriately publish on each copy an appropriate copyright notice and disclaimer of warranty; keep intact all the notices that refer to this License and to the absence of any warranty; and distribute a copy of this License along with the Library.

   You may charge a fee for the physical act of transferring a copy, and you may at your option offer warranty protection in exchange for a fee.

   2. You may modify your copy or copies of the Library or any portion of it, thus forming a work based on the Library, and copy and distribute such modifications or work under the terms of Section 1 above, provided that you also meet all of these conditions:

      a) The modified work must itself be a software library.

      b) You must cause the files modified to carry prominent notices stating that you changed the files and the date of any change.

      c) You must cause the whole of the work to be licensed at no charge to all third parties under the terms of this License.

      d) If a facility in the modified Library refers to a function or a table of data to be supplied by an application program that uses the facility, other than as an argument passed when the facility is invoked, then you must make a good faith effort to ensure that, in the event an application does not supply such function or table, the facility still operates, and performs whatever part of its purpose remains meaningful.

      (For example, a function in a library to compute square roots has a purpose that is entirely well-defined independent of the application. Therefore, Subsection 2d requires that any application-supplied function or table used by this function must be optional: if the application does not supply it, the square root function must still compute square roots.)

   These requirements apply to the modified work as a whole. If identifiable sections of that work are not derived from the Library, and can be reasonably considered independent and separate works in themselves, then this License, and its terms, do not apply to those sections when you distribute them as separate works. But when you distribute the same sections as part of a whole which is a work based on the Library, the distribution of the whole must be on the terms of this License, whose permissions for other licensees extend to the entire whole, and thus to each and every part regardless of who wrote it.

   Thus, it is not the intent of this section to claim rights or contest your rights to work written entirely by you; rather, the intent is to exercise the right to control the distribution of derivative or collective works based on the Library.

   In addition, mere aggregation of another work not based on the Library with the Library (or with a work based on the Library) on a volume of a storage or distribution medium does not bring the other work under the scope of this License.

   3. You may opt to apply the terms of the ordinary GNU General Public License instead of this License to a given copy of the Library. To do this, you must alter all the notices that refer to this License, so that they refer to the ordinary GNU General Public License, version 2, instead of to this License. (If a newer version than version 2 of the ordinary GNU General Public License has appeared, then you can specify that version instead if you wish.) Do not make any other change in these notices.

   Once this change is made in a given copy, it is irreversible for that copy, so the ordinary GNU General Public License applies to all subsequent copies and derivative works made from that copy.

   This option is useful when you wish to copy part of the code of the Library into a program that is not a library.

   4. You may copy and distribute the Library (or a portion or derivative of it, under Section 2) in object code or executable form under the terms of Sections 1 and 2 above provided that you accompany it with the complete corresponding machine-readable source code, which must be distributed under the terms of Sections 1 and 2 above on a medium customarily used for software interchange.

   If distribution of object code is made by offering access to copy from a designated place, then offering equivalent access to copy the source code from the same place satisfies the requirement to distribute the source code, even though third parties are not compelled to copy the source along with the object code.

   5. A program that contains no derivative of any portion of the Library, but is designed to work with the Library by being compiled or linked with it, is called a "work that uses the Library". Such a work, in isolation, is not a derivative work of the Library, and therefore falls outside the scope of this License.

   However, linking a "work that uses the Library" with the Library creates an executable that is a derivative of the Library (because it contains portions of the Library), rather than a "work that uses the library". The executable is therefore covered by this License. Section 6 states terms for distribution of such executables.

   When a "work that uses the Library" uses material from a header file that is part of the Library, the object code for the work may be a derivative work of the Library even though the source code is not. Whether this is true is especially significant if the work can be linked without the Library, or if the work is itself a library. The threshold for this to be true is not precisely defined by law.

   If such an object file uses only numerical parameters, data structure layouts and accessors, and small macros and small inline functions (ten lines or less in length), then the use of the object file is unrestricted, regardless of whether it is legally a derivative work. (Executables containing this object code plus portions of the Library will still fall under Section 6.)

   Otherwise, if the work is a derivative of the Library, you may distribute the object code for the work under the terms of Section 6. Any executables containing that work also fall under Section 6, whether or not they are linked directly with the Library itself.

   6. As an exception to the Sections above, you may also compile or link a "work that uses the Library" with the Library to produce a work containing portions of the Library, and distribute that work under terms of your choice, provided that the terms permit modification of the work for the customer's own use and reverse engineering for debugging such modifications.

   You must give prominent notice with each copy of the work that the Library is used in it and that the Library and its use are covered by this License. You must supply a copy of this License. If the work during execution displays copyright notices, you must include the copyright notice for the Library among them, as well as a reference directing the user to the copy of this License. Also, you must do one of these things:

      a) Accompany the work with the complete corresponding machine-readable source code for the Library including whatever changes were used in the work (which must be distributed under Sections 1 and 2 above); and, if the work is an executable linked with the Library, with the complete machine-readable "work that uses the Library", as object code and/or source code, so that the user can modify the Library and then relink to produce a modified executable containing the modified Library. (It is understood that the user who changes the contents of definitions files in the Library will not necessarily be able to recompile the application to use the modified definitions.)

      b) Accompany the work with a written offer, valid for at least three years, to give the same user the materials specified in Subsection 6a, above, for a charge no more than the cost of performing this distribution.

      c) If distribution of the work is made by offering access to copy from a designated place, offer equivalent access to copy the above specified materials from the same place.

      d) Verify that the user has already received a copy of these materials or that you have already sent this user a copy.

   For an executable, the required form of the "work that uses the Library" must include any data and utility programs needed for reproducing the executable from it. However, as a special exception, the source code distributed need not include anything that is normally distributed (in either source or binary form) with the major components (compiler, kernel, and so on) of the operating system on which the executable runs, unless that component itself accompanies the executable.

   It may happen that this requirement contradicts the license restrictions of other proprietary libraries that do not normally accompany the operating system. Such a contradiction means you cannot use both them and the Library together in an executable that you distribute.

   7. You may place library facilities that are a work based on the Library side-by-side in a single library together with other library facilities not covered by this License, and distribute such a combined library, provided that the separate distribution of the work based on the Library and of the other library facilities is otherwise permitted, and provided that you do these two things:

      a) Accompany the combined library with a copy of the same work based on the Library, uncombined with any other library facilities. This must be distributed under the terms of the Sections above.

      b) Give prominent notice with the combined library of the fact that part of it is a work based on the Library, and explaining where to find the accompanying uncombined form of the same work.

   8. You may not copy, modify, sublicense, link with, or distribute the Library except as expressly provided under this License. Any attempt otherwise to copy, modify, sublicense, link with, or distribute the Library is void, and will automatically terminate your rights under this License. However, parties who have received copies, or rights, from you under this License will not have their licenses terminated so long as such parties remain in full compliance.

   9. You are not required to accept this License, since you have not signed it. However, nothing else grants you permission to modify or distribute the Library or its derivative works. These actions are prohibited by law if you do not accept this License. Therefore, by modifying or distributing the Library (or any work based on the Library), you indicate your acceptance of this License to do so, and all its terms and conditions for copying, distributing or modifying the Library or works based on it.

   10. Each time you redistribute the Library (or any work based on the Library), the recipient automatically receives a license from the original licensor to copy, distribute, link with or modify the Library subject to these terms and conditions. You may not impose any further restrictions on the recipients' exercise of the rights granted herein. You are not responsible for enforcing compliance by third parties to this License.

   11. If, as a consequence of a court judgment or allegation of patent infringement or for any other reason (not limited to patent issues), conditions are imposed on you (whether by court order, agreement or otherwise) that contradict the conditions of this License, they do not excuse you from the conditions of this License. If you cannot distribute so as to satisfy simultaneously your obligations under this License and any other pertinent obligations, then as a consequence you may not distribute the Library at all. For example, if a patent license would not permit royalty-free redistribution of the Library by all those who receive copies directly or indirectly through you, then the only way you could satisfy both it and this License would be to refrain entirely from distribution of the Library.

   If any portion of this section is held invalid or unenforceable under any particular circumstance, the balance of the section is intended to apply, and the section as a whole is intended to apply in other circumstances.

   It is not the purpose of this section to induce you to infringe any patents or other property right claims or to contest validity of any such claims; this section has the sole purpose of protecting the integrity of the free software distribution system which is implemented by public license practices. Many people have made generous contributions to the wide range of software distributed through that system in reliance on consistent application of that system; it is up to the author/donor to decide if he or she is willing to distribute software through any other system and a licensee cannot impose that choice.

   This section is intended to make thoroughly clear what is believed to be a consequence of the rest of this License.

   12. If the distribution and/or use of the Library is restricted in certain countries either by patents or by copyrighted interfaces, the original copyright holder who places the Library under this License may add an explicit geographical distribution limitation excluding those countries, so that distribution is permitted only in or among countries not thus excluded. In such case, this License incorporates the limitation as if written in the body of this License.

   13. The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or new versions of the Library General Public License from time to time. Such new versions will be similar in spirit to the present version, but may differ in detail to address new problems or concerns.

   Each version is given a distinguishing version number. If the Library specifies a version number of this License which applies to it and "any later version", you have the option of following the terms and conditions either of that version or of any later version published by the Free Software Foundation. If the Library does not specify a license version number, you may choose any version ever published by the Free Software Foundation.

   14. If you wish to incorporate parts of the Library into other free programs whose distribution conditions are incompatible with these, write to the author to ask for permission. For software which is copyrighted by the Free Software Foundation, write to the Free Software Foundation; we sometimes make exceptions for this. Our decision will be guided by the two goals of preserving the free status of all derivatives of our free software and of promoting the sharing and reuse of software generally.

   NO WARRANTY

   15. BECAUSE THE LIBRARY IS LICENSED FREE OF CHARGE, THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE LIBRARY, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW. EXCEPT WHEN OTHERWISE STATED IN WRITING THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND/OR OTHER PARTIES PROVIDE THE LIBRARY "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE LIBRARY IS WITH YOU. SHOULD THE LIBRARY PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

   16. IN NO EVENT UNLESS REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW OR AGREED TO IN WRITING WILL ANY COPYRIGHT HOLDER, OR ANY OTHER PARTY WHO MAY MODIFY AND/OR REDISTRIBUTE THE LIBRARY AS PERMITTED ABOVE, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR DAMAGES, INCLUDING ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE LIBRARY (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF DATA OR DATA BEING RENDERED INACCURATE OR LOSSES SUSTAINED BY YOU OR THIRD PARTIES OR A FAILURE OF THE LIBRARY TO OPERATE WITH ANY OTHER SOFTWARE), EVEN IF SUCH HOLDER OR OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

How to Apply These Terms to Your New Libraries

If you develop a new library, and you want it to be of the greatest possible use to the public, we recommend making it free software that everyone can redistribute and change. You can do so by permitting redistribution under these terms (or, alternatively, under the terms of the ordinary General Public License).

To apply these terms, attach the following notices to the library. It is safest to attach them to the start of each source file to most effectively convey the exclusion of warranty; and each file should have at least the "copyright" line and a pointer to where the full notice is found.

one line to give the library's name and an idea of what it does.

Copyright (C) year name of author

This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU Library General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This library is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU Library General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Library General Public License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA.

Also add information on how to contact you by electronic and paper mail.

You should also get your employer (if you work as a programmer) or your school, if any, to sign a "copyright disclaimer" for the library, if necessary. Here is a sample; alter the names:

Yoyodyne, Inc., hereby disclaims all copyright interest in

the library `Frob' (a library for tweaking knobs) written

by James Random Hacker.

signature of Ty Coon, 1 April 1990

Ty Coon, President of Vice

That's all there is to it!</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/setup.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ab96c15eacef3f5dec9d4641273f4b9cd591f725b071c862d4e4e8a90513109b</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>15339d0dcb2feb010068d654ecaa6362</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7f1a3bbe28ed8424f73000f7ffeb2bf4ce2d61f1</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576894">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>GNU Library General Public License v2.1 or later</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>GNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE

Version 2.1, February 1999

Copyright (C) 1991, 1999 Free Software Foundation, Inc.

51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA

Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.

[This is the first released version of the Lesser GPL. It also counts as the successor of the GNU Library Public License, version 2, hence the version number 2.1.]

Preamble

The licenses for most software are designed to take away your freedom to share and change it. By contrast, the GNU General Public Licenses are intended to guarantee your freedom to share and change free software--to make sure the software is free for all its users.

This license, the Lesser General Public License, applies to some specially designated software packages--typically libraries--of the Free Software Foundation and other authors who decide to use it. You can use it too, but we suggest you first think carefully about whether this license or the ordinary General Public License is the better strategy to use in any particular case, based on the explanations below.

When we speak of free software, we are referring to freedom of use, not price. Our General Public Licenses are designed to make sure that you have the freedom to distribute copies of free software (and charge for this service if you wish); that you receive source code or can get it if you want it; that you can change the software and use pieces of it in new free programs; and that you are informed that you can do these things.

To protect your rights, we need to make restrictions that forbid distributors to deny you these rights or to ask you to surrender these rights. These restrictions translate to certain responsibilities for you if you distribute copies of the library or if you modify it.

For example, if you distribute copies of the library, whether gratis or for a fee, you must give the recipients all the rights that we gave you. You must make sure that they, too, receive or can get the source code. If you link other code with the library, you must provide complete object files to the recipients, so that they can relink them with the library after making changes to the library and recompiling it. And you must show them these terms so they know their rights.

We protect your rights with a two-step method: (1) we copyright the library, and (2) we offer you this license, which gives you legal permission to copy, distribute and/or modify the library.

To protect each distributor, we want to make it very clear that there is no warranty for the free library. Also, if the library is modified by someone else and passed on, the recipients should know that what they have is not the original version, so that the original author's reputation will not be affected by problems that might be introduced by others.

Finally, software patents pose a constant threat to the existence of any free program. We wish to make sure that a company cannot effectively restrict the users of a free program by obtaining a restrictive license from a patent holder. Therefore, we insist that any patent license obtained for a version of the library must be consistent with the full freedom of use specified in this license.

Most GNU software, including some libraries, is covered by the ordinary GNU General Public License. This license, the GNU Lesser General Public License, applies to certain designated libraries, and is quite different from the ordinary General Public License. We use this license for certain libraries in order to permit linking those libraries into non-free programs.

When a program is linked with a library, whether statically or using a shared library, the combination of the two is legally speaking a combined work, a derivative of the original library. The ordinary General Public License therefore permits such linking only if the entire combination fits its criteria of freedom. The Lesser General Public License permits more lax criteria for linking other code with the library.

We call this license the "Lesser" General Public License because it does Less to protect the user's freedom than the ordinary General Public License. It also provides other free software developers Less of an advantage over competing non-free programs. These disadvantages are the reason we use the ordinary General Public License for many libraries. However, the Lesser license provides advantages in certain special circumstances.

For example, on rare occasions, there may be a special need to encourage the widest possible use of a certain library, so that it becomes a de-facto standard. To achieve this, non-free programs must be allowed to use the library. A more frequent case is that a free library does the same job as widely used non-free libraries. In this case, there is little to gain by limiting the free library to free software only, so we use the Lesser General Public License.

In other cases, permission to use a particular library in non-free programs enables a greater number of people to use a large body of free software. For example, permission to use the GNU C Library in non-free programs enables many more people to use the whole GNU operating system, as well as its variant, the GNU/Linux operating system.

Although the Lesser General Public License is Less protective of the users' freedom, it does ensure that the user of a program that is linked with the Library has the freedom and the wherewithal to run that program using a modified version of the Library.

The precise terms and conditions for copying, distribution and modification follow. Pay close attention to the difference between a "work based on the library" and a "work that uses the library". The former contains code derived from the library, whereas the latter must be combined with the library in order to run.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR COPYING, DISTRIBUTION AND MODIFICATION

   0. This License Agreement applies to any software library or other program which contains a notice placed by the copyright holder or other authorized party saying it may be distributed under the terms of this Lesser General Public License (also called "this License"). Each licensee is addressed as "you".

   A "library" means a collection of software functions and/or data prepared so as to be conveniently linked with application programs (which use some of those functions and data) to form executables.

   The "Library", below, refers to any such software library or work which has been distributed under these terms. A "work based on the Library" means either the Library or any derivative work under copyright law: that is to say, a work containing the Library or a portion of it, either verbatim or with modifications and/or translated straightforwardly into another language. (Hereinafter, translation is included without limitation in the term "modification".)

   "Source code" for a work means the preferred form of the work for making modifications to it. For a library, complete source code means all the source code for all modules it contains, plus any associated interface definition files, plus the scripts used to control compilation and installation of the library.

   Activities other than copying, distribution and modification are not covered by this License; they are outside its scope. The act of running a program using the Library is not restricted, and output from such a program is covered only if its contents constitute a work based on the Library (independent of the use of the Library in a tool for writing it). Whether that is true depends on what the Library does and what the program that uses the Library does.

   1. You may copy and distribute verbatim copies of the Library's complete source code as you receive it, in any medium, provided that you conspicuously and appropriately publish on each copy an appropriate copyright notice and disclaimer of warranty; keep intact all the notices that refer to this License and to the absence of any warranty; and distribute a copy of this License along with the Library.

   You may charge a fee for the physical act of transferring a copy, and you may at your option offer warranty protection in exchange for a fee.

   2. You may modify your copy or copies of the Library or any portion of it, thus forming a work based on the Library, and copy and distribute such modifications or work under the terms of Section 1 above, provided that you also meet all of these conditions:

      a) The modified work must itself be a software library.

      b) You must cause the files modified to carry prominent notices stating that you changed the files and the date of any change.

      c) You must cause the whole of the work to be licensed at no charge to all third parties under the terms of this License.

      d) If a facility in the modified Library refers to a function or a table of data to be supplied by an application program that uses the facility, other than as an argument passed when the facility is invoked, then you must make a good faith effort to ensure that, in the event an application does not supply such function or table, the facility still operates, and performs whatever part of its purpose remains meaningful.

   (For example, a function in a library to compute square roots has a purpose that is entirely well-defined independent of the application. Therefore, Subsection 2d requires that any application-supplied function or table used by this function must be optional: if the application does not supply it, the square root function must still compute square roots.)

   These requirements apply to the modified work as a whole. If identifiable sections of that work are not derived from the Library, and can be reasonably considered independent and separate works in themselves, then this License, and its terms, do not apply to those sections when you distribute them as separate works. But when you distribute the same sections as part of a whole which is a work based on the Library, the distribution of the whole must be on the terms of this License, whose permissions for other licensees extend to the entire whole, and thus to each and every part regardless of who wrote it.

   Thus, it is not the intent of this section to claim rights or contest your rights to work written entirely by you; rather, the intent is to exercise the right to control the distribution of derivative or collective works based on the Library.

   In addition, mere aggregation of another work not based on the Library with the Library (or with a work based on the Library) on a volume of a storage or distribution medium does not bring the other work under the scope of this License.

   3. You may opt to apply the terms of the ordinary GNU General Public License instead of this License to a given copy of the Library. To do this, you must alter all the notices that refer to this License, so that they refer to the ordinary GNU General Public License, version 2, instead of to this License. (If a newer version than version 2 of the ordinary GNU General Public License has appeared, then you can specify that version instead if you wish.) Do not make any other change in these notices.

   Once this change is made in a given copy, it is irreversible for that copy, so the ordinary GNU General Public License applies to all subsequent copies and derivative works made from that copy.

   This option is useful when you wish to copy part of the code of the Library into a program that is not a library.

   4. You may copy and distribute the Library (or a portion or derivative of it, under Section 2) in object code or executable form under the terms of Sections 1 and 2 above provided that you accompany it with the complete corresponding machine-readable source code, which must be distributed under the terms of Sections 1 and 2 above on a medium customarily used for software interchange.

   If distribution of object code is made by offering access to copy from a designated place, then offering equivalent access to copy the source code from the same place satisfies the requirement to distribute the source code, even though third parties are not compelled to copy the source along with the object code.

   5. A program that contains no derivative of any portion of the Library, but is designed to work with the Library by being compiled or linked with it, is called a "work that uses the Library". Such a work, in isolation, is not a derivative work of the Library, and therefore falls outside the scope of this License.

   However, linking a "work that uses the Library" with the Library creates an executable that is a derivative of the Library (because it contains portions of the Library), rather than a "work that uses the library". The executable is therefore covered by this License. Section 6 states terms for distribution of such executables.

   When a "work that uses the Library" uses material from a header file that is part of the Library, the object code for the work may be a derivative work of the Library even though the source code is not. Whether this is true is especially significant if the work can be linked without the Library, or if the work is itself a library. The threshold for this to be true is not precisely defined by law.

   If such an object file uses only numerical parameters, data structure layouts and accessors, and small macros and small inline functions (ten lines or less in length), then the use of the object file is unrestricted, regardless of whether it is legally a derivative work. (Executables containing this object code plus portions of the Library will still fall under Section 6.)

   Otherwise, if the work is a derivative of the Library, you may distribute the object code for the work under the terms of Section 6. Any executables containing that work also fall under Section 6, whether or not they are linked directly with the Library itself.

   6. As an exception to the Sections above, you may also combine or link a "work that uses the Library" with the Library to produce a work containing portions of the Library, and distribute that work under terms of your choice, provided that the terms permit modification of the work for the customer's own use and reverse engineering for debugging such modifications.

   You must give prominent notice with each copy of the work that the Library is used in it and that the Library and its use are covered by this License. You must supply a copy of this License. If the work during execution displays copyright notices, you must include the copyright notice for the Library among them, as well as a reference directing the user to the copy of this License. Also, you must do one of these things:

      a) Accompany the work with the complete corresponding machine-readable source code for the Library including whatever changes were used in the work (which must be distributed under Sections 1 and 2 above); and, if the work is an executable linked with the Library, with the complete machine-readable "work that uses the Library", as object code and/or source code, so that the user can modify the Library and then relink to produce a modified executable containing the modified Library. (It is understood that the user who changes the contents of definitions files in the Library will not necessarily be able to recompile the application to use the modified definitions.)

      b) Use a suitable shared library mechanism for linking with the Library. A suitable mechanism is one that (1) uses at run time a copy of the library already present on the user's computer system, rather than copying library functions into the executable, and (2) will operate properly with a modified version of the library, if the user installs one, as long as the modified version is interface-compatible with the version that the work was made with.

      c) Accompany the work with a written offer, valid for at least three years, to give the same user the materials specified in Subsection 6a, above, for a charge no more than the cost of performing this distribution.

      d) If distribution of the work is made by offering access to copy from a designated place, offer equivalent access to copy the above specified materials from the same place.

      e) Verify that the user has already received a copy of these materials or that you have already sent this user a copy.

   For an executable, the required form of the "work that uses the Library" must include any data and utility programs needed for reproducing the executable from it. However, as a special exception, the materials to be distributed need not include anything that is normally distributed (in either source or binary form) with the major components (compiler, kernel, and so on) of the operating system on which the executable runs, unless that component itself accompanies the executable.

   It may happen that this requirement contradicts the license restrictions of other proprietary libraries that do not normally accompany the operating system. Such a contradiction means you cannot use both them and the Library together in an executable that you distribute.

   7. You may place library facilities that are a work based on the Library side-by-side in a single library together with other library facilities not covered by this License, and distribute such a combined library, provided that the separate distribution of the work based on the Library and of the other library facilities is otherwise permitted, and provided that you do these two things:

      a) Accompany the combined library with a copy of the same work based on the Library, uncombined with any other library facilities. This must be distributed under the terms of the Sections above.

      b) Give prominent notice with the combined library of the fact that part of it is a work based on the Library, and explaining where to find the accompanying uncombined form of the same work.

   8. You may not copy, modify, sublicense, link with, or distribute the Library except as expressly provided under this License. Any attempt otherwise to copy, modify, sublicense, link with, or distribute the Library is void, and will automatically terminate your rights under this License. However, parties who have received copies, or rights, from you under this License will not have their licenses terminated so long as such parties remain in full compliance.

   9. You are not required to accept this License, since you have not signed it. However, nothing else grants you permission to modify or distribute the Library or its derivative works. These actions are prohibited by law if you do not accept this License. Therefore, by modifying or distributing the Library (or any work based on the Library), you indicate your acceptance of this License to do so, and all its terms and conditions for copying, distributing or modifying the Library or works based on it.

   10. Each time you redistribute the Library (or any work based on the Library), the recipient automatically receives a license from the original licensor to copy, distribute, link with or modify the Library subject to these terms and conditions. You may not impose any further restrictions on the recipients' exercise of the rights granted herein. You are not responsible for enforcing compliance by third parties with this License.

   11. If, as a consequence of a court judgment or allegation of patent infringement or for any other reason (not limited to patent issues), conditions are imposed on you (whether by court order, agreement or otherwise) that contradict the conditions of this License, they do not excuse you from the conditions of this License. If you cannot distribute so as to satisfy simultaneously your obligations under this License and any other pertinent obligations, then as a consequence you may not distribute the Library at all. For example, if a patent license would not permit royalty-free redistribution of the Library by all those who receive copies directly or indirectly through you, then the only way you could satisfy both it and this License would be to refrain entirely from distribution of the Library.

   If any portion of this section is held invalid or unenforceable under any particular circumstance, the balance of the section is intended to apply, and the section as a whole is intended to apply in other circumstances.

   It is not the purpose of this section to induce you to infringe any patents or other property right claims or to contest validity of any such claims; this section has the sole purpose of protecting the integrity of the free software distribution system which is implemented by public license practices. Many people have made generous contributions to the wide range of software distributed through that system in reliance on consistent application of that system; it is up to the author/donor to decide if he or she is willing to distribute software through any other system and a licensee cannot impose that choice.

   This section is intended to make thoroughly clear what is believed to be a consequence of the rest of this License.

   12. If the distribution and/or use of the Library is restricted in certain countries either by patents or by copyrighted interfaces, the original copyright holder who places the Library under this License may add an explicit geographical distribution limitation excluding those countries, so that distribution is permitted only in or among countries not thus excluded. In such case, this License incorporates the limitation as if written in the body of this License.

   13. The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or new versions of the Lesser General Public License from time to time. Such new versions will be similar in spirit to the present version, but may differ in detail to address new problems or concerns.

   Each version is given a distinguishing version number. If the Library specifies a version number of this License which applies to it and "any later version", you have the option of following the terms and conditions either of that version or of any later version published by the Free Software Foundation. If the Library does not specify a license version number, you may choose any version ever published by the Free Software Foundation.

   14. If you wish to incorporate parts of the Library into other free programs whose distribution conditions are incompatible with these, write to the author to ask for permission. For software which is copyrighted by the Free Software Foundation, write to the Free Software Foundation; we sometimes make exceptions for this. Our decision will be guided by the two goals of preserving the free status of all derivatives of our free software and of promoting the sharing and reuse of software generally.

   NO WARRANTY

   15. BECAUSE THE LIBRARY IS LICENSED FREE OF CHARGE, THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE LIBRARY, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW. EXCEPT WHEN OTHERWISE STATED IN WRITING THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND/OR OTHER PARTIES PROVIDE THE LIBRARY "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE LIBRARY IS WITH YOU. SHOULD THE LIBRARY PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

   16. IN NO EVENT UNLESS REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW OR AGREED TO IN WRITING WILL ANY COPYRIGHT HOLDER, OR ANY OTHER PARTY WHO MAY MODIFY AND/OR REDISTRIBUTE THE LIBRARY AS PERMITTED ABOVE, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR DAMAGES, INCLUDING ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE LIBRARY (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF DATA OR DATA BEING RENDERED INACCURATE OR LOSSES SUSTAINED BY YOU OR THIRD PARTIES OR A FAILURE OF THE LIBRARY TO OPERATE WITH ANY OTHER SOFTWARE), EVEN IF SUCH HOLDER OR OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

How to Apply These Terms to Your New Libraries

If you develop a new library, and you want it to be of the greatest possible use to the public, we recommend making it free software that everyone can redistribute and change. You can do so by permitting redistribution under these terms (or, alternatively, under the terms of the ordinary General Public License).

To apply these terms, attach the following notices to the library. It is safest to attach them to the start of each source file to most effectively convey the exclusion of warranty; and each file should have at least the "copyright" line and a pointer to where the full notice is found.

&lt;one line to give the library's name and an idea of what it does.&gt;

Copyright (C) &lt;year&gt; &lt;name of author&gt;

This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This library is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA

Also add information on how to contact you by electronic and paper mail.

You should also get your employer (if you work as a programmer) or your school, if any, to sign a "copyright disclaimer" for the library, if necessary. Here is a sample; alter the names:

Yoyodyne, Inc., hereby disclaims all copyright interest in

the library `Frob' (a library for tweaking knobs) written

by James Random Hacker.

&lt; signature of Ty Coon &gt; , 1 April 1990

Ty Coon, President of Vice

That's all there is to it!</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/remote.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>60c5f09c0ff040146bcf44b65e39bb7f46c39550abccc6bb6790a0b63ee24260</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>5c261d1b5eaa456c82f58563221e6b4b</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>86a7a395964d8e5cde1b5349f152fed2fed703ca</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 2002 Henrik Ekelund, version 2.1 by Vernon Cole</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576917">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/setuptestframework.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>cd1cb5a5187d8934558d34737a598cb6</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ce5ba2d4a232d05a2f8f13276d2b7d384c1e024e</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>2642d8577b9b1d67a0df3a3cb7e67f6aeda24e04300f7884282d6f728e77b143</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:licenseDeclared rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576910">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/xls_write.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>9b2b3a0345fba73e862e62bc836319f2716d2cba</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>74ab04ed147330fd5e02e5c5a4eb476fb8a8af0508e78381061cf2b6f0130d88</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>11035a07a2882a5818a1ac9b1b5aa25d</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576926">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/setup.cfg</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>d18630e86a7af6f69c55b8c7f131cc8a</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>264c980f3ae4033b8dd33d29db33ce13e90b0a19</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ade81f7bec85359de971bdc033225cb1a9905766f8ca751327a21b107289df18</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576900">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/MANIFEST.in</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>0b87c09b3aeba535b2c9067e386f00b6</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>694fb811ab96426fe259ef771c68aac9a096dff1</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>9577548efd8ac7392f333640119af3139012070b7273766dee9e12103437dce0</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576928">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.0-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/PKG-INFO</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>fb59e4310a3b185cd94cce4ca1a403bf</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>633612916ad127a6248b44e239d78096a1f2ca30</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>41322095cf1f3e21c57d8b7d54ea569bb08f2f647ef633647f9868d5e364c213</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576925">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/schema_table.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7ec95f793606c27b42f13330d92da7bf77936f0f6382545c1be18a3f2780fa33</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7948da62da328ea8cfc1d2391b53eff5</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>93da2b2e8efcbff68bf86100ccad781a3d0147e4</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576903">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/db_table_names.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>0e79174fdf00132979a19f4cc33489669a346b1e197f35f1cda176fb308d627c</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>3ffd290d5415d1e2843a2addc9a4cb6e</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>b2eac5cd09dd1ec02c2f44efc00b7ec7b143b68a</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576905">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/run_server_py_25.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>32cdec956e594f4b41931cfd69dd55f6</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8ae6e2c2bfb153af4b41dbacfbd0b9e63c2b71e7</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c17a6c36b0fb938274100c02e671d8e723b7eef16f96d94c22da7a29a7cf1218</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576932">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.0-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/README.txt</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e79e4b89d08954b8a9949148f6e6c8e14e2813d1</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>2e4ee2f591480a5ed3e2750bb04cca0621f0f1b195c9a2f320c14ed0541ddbdd</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>57c9e012d4edd985537cfdab7a480c8f</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576922">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/startserver.bat</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>322aea4b73c3ff3a4b8fd53e5322d529e77ac29a1dba0c81f318f1f3857a54da</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>5fc8031ab9acf996cb7c8cd94f1a0f82</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>694d79f13becb66ecde1ef07a71fc26d132c0996</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576899">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/older_whatsnew.txt</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>128b28dd99f52c4f6155250d05ead853</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ebc2d9f42c60c9d8e1fbb6e0d99d4065131dee0e</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c92c2b4f94c63e417da5576192ed6dd2eacb8408d24e1e60dd11d0f0a3066004</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:checksum>
              <spdx:Checksum>
                <spdx:checksumValue>4bbfce499849937c3b09d3a7be8e61a9a07c1e161390419fbfe78a0eef7b4148</spdx:checksumValue>
                <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
              </spdx:Checksum>
            </spdx:checksum>
            <spdx:checksum>
              <spdx:Checksum>
                <spdx:checksumValue>48b15ec689304edc253ef660e4a37298</spdx:checksumValue>
                <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
              </spdx:Checksum>
            </spdx:checksum>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576929">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/ado_consts.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>97fb4474cef9dcfacd24ad7a8b66ce1f</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>710977bd4bf3d6b246cb1c98d792ba4214f54f47</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ce3520ee60137104f5c67ad6548d7b3de58ed0b9b10055050e816631d3b2c265</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576927">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c627ebed0fc837f3f926b18f9a1712028d60f233</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/license.txt</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>The file contains the text of the LGPL. The text of the license is licensed under:
Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies
of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
Thus we concluded License-of-GNU-Licenses as license of this file</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-License-of-GNU-Licenses">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-License-of-GNU-Licenses</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>License-of-GNU-Licenses</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies
of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseConcluded>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>610e0c3a24a26acb0470f8f5eb0298df966fc380cee8e0febdac6791b6209d6c</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 1991, 1999 Free Software Foundation, Inc.</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>652b4e2f7a8a93e7abdd2de7031e0bdb</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-only">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-only</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>GNU Lesser General Public License v2.1 only</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>GNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE

Version 2.1, February 1999

Copyright (C) 1991, 1999 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301  USA

Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.

[This is the first released version of the Lesser GPL.  It also counts as the successor of the GNU Library Public License, version 2, hence the version number 2.1.]

Preamble

The licenses for most software are designed to take away your freedom to share and change it. By contrast, the GNU General Public Licenses are intended to guarantee your freedom to share and change free software--to make sure the software is free for all its users.

This license, the Lesser General Public License, applies to some specially designated software packages--typically libraries--of the Free Software Foundation and other authors who decide to use it. You can use it too, but we suggest you first think carefully about whether this license or the ordinary General Public License is the better strategy to use in any particular case, based on the explanations below.

When we speak of free software, we are referring to freedom of use, not price. Our General Public Licenses are designed to make sure that you have the freedom to distribute copies of free software (and charge for this service if you wish); that you receive source code or can get it if you want it; that you can change the software and use pieces of it in new free programs; and that you are informed that you can do these things.

To protect your rights, we need to make restrictions that forbid distributors to deny you these rights or to ask you to surrender these rights. These restrictions translate to certain responsibilities for you if you distribute copies of the library or if you modify it.

For example, if you distribute copies of the library, whether gratis or for a fee, you must give the recipients all the rights that we gave you. You must make sure that they, too, receive or can get the source code. If you link other code with the library, you must provide complete object files to the recipients, so that they can relink them with the library after making changes to the library and recompiling it. And you must show them these terms so they know their rights.

We protect your rights with a two-step method: (1) we copyright the library, and (2) we offer you this license, which gives you legal permission to copy, distribute and/or modify the library.

To protect each distributor, we want to make it very clear that there is no warranty for the free library. Also, if the library is modified by someone else and passed on, the recipients should know that what they have is not the original version, so that the original author's reputation will not be affected by problems that might be introduced by others.

Finally, software patents pose a constant threat to the existence of any free program. We wish to make sure that a company cannot effectively restrict the users of a free program by obtaining a restrictive license from a patent holder. Therefore, we insist that any patent license obtained for a version of the library must be consistent with the full freedom of use specified in this license.

Most GNU software, including some libraries, is covered by the ordinary GNU General Public License. This license, the GNU Lesser General Public License, applies to certain designated libraries, and is quite different from the ordinary General Public License. We use this license for certain libraries in order to permit linking those libraries into non-free programs.

When a program is linked with a library, whether statically or using a shared library, the combination of the two is legally speaking a combined work, a derivative of the original library. The ordinary General Public License therefore permits such linking only if the entire combination fits its criteria of freedom. The Lesser General Public License permits more lax criteria for linking other code with the library.

We call this license the "Lesser" General Public License because it does Less to protect the user's freedom than the ordinary General Public License. It also provides other free software developers Less of an advantage over competing non-free programs. These disadvantages are the reason we use the ordinary General Public License for many libraries. However, the Lesser license provides advantages in certain special circumstances.

For example, on rare occasions, there may be a special need to encourage the widest possible use of a certain library, so that it becomes a de-facto standard. To achieve this, non-free programs must be allowed to use the library. A more frequent case is that a free library does the same job as widely used non-free libraries. In this case, there is little to gain by limiting the free library to free software only, so we use the Lesser General Public License.

In other cases, permission to use a particular library in non-free programs enables a greater number of people to use a large body of free software. For example, permission to use the GNU C Library in non-free programs enables many more people to use the whole GNU operating system, as well as its variant, the GNU/Linux operating system.

Although the Lesser General Public License is Less protective of the users' freedom, it does ensure that the user of a program that is linked with the Library has the freedom and the wherewithal to run that program using a modified version of the Library.

The precise terms and conditions for copying, distribution and modification follow. Pay close attention to the difference between a "work based on the library" and a "work that uses the library". The former contains code derived from the library, whereas the latter must be combined with the library in order to run.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR COPYING, DISTRIBUTION AND MODIFICATION

0. This License Agreement applies to any software library or other program which contains a notice placed by the copyright holder or other authorized party saying it may be distributed under the terms of this Lesser General Public License (also called "this License"). Each licensee is addressed as "you".

A "library" means a collection of software functions and/or data prepared so as to be conveniently linked with application programs (which use some of those functions and data) to form executables.

The "Library", below, refers to any such software library or work which has been distributed under these terms. A "work based on the Library" means either the Library or any derivative work under copyright law: that is to say, a work containing the Library or a portion of it, either verbatim or with modifications and/or translated straightforwardly into another language. (Hereinafter, translation is included without limitation in the term "modification".)

"Source code" for a work means the preferred form of the work for making modifications to it. For a library, complete source code means all the source code for all modules it contains, plus any associated interface definition files, plus the scripts used to control compilation and installation of the library.

Activities other than copying, distribution and modification are not covered by this License; they are outside its scope. The act of running a program using the Library is not restricted, and output from such a program is covered only if its contents constitute a work based on the Library (independent of the use of the Library in a tool for writing it). Whether that is true depends on what the Library does and what the program that uses the Library does.

1. You may copy and distribute verbatim copies of the Library's complete source code as you receive it, in any medium, provided that you conspicuously and appropriately publish on each copy an appropriate copyright notice and disclaimer of warranty; keep intact all the notices that refer to this License and to the absence of any warranty; and distribute a copy of this License along with the Library.

You may charge a fee for the physical act of transferring a copy, and you may at your option offer warranty protection in exchange for a fee.

2. You may modify your copy or copies of the Library or any portion of it, thus forming a work based on the Library, and copy and distribute such modifications or work under the terms of Section 1 above, provided that you also meet all of these conditions:

     a) The modified work must itself be a software library.

     b) You must cause the files modified to carry prominent notices stating that you changed the files and the date of any change.

     c) You must cause the whole of the work to be licensed at no charge to all third parties under the terms of this License.

     d) If a facility in the modified Library refers to a function or a table of data to be supplied by an application program that uses the facility, other than as an argument passed when the facility is invoked, then you must make a good faith effort to ensure that, in the event an application does not supply such function or table, the facility still operates, and performs whatever part of its purpose remains meaningful.

(For example, a function in a library to compute square roots has a purpose that is entirely well-defined independent of the application. Therefore, Subsection 2d requires that any application-supplied function or table used by this function must be optional: if the application does not supply it, the square root function must still compute square roots.)

These requirements apply to the modified work as a whole. If identifiable sections of that work are not derived from the Library, and can be reasonably considered independent and separate works in themselves, then this License, and its terms, do not apply to those sections when you distribute them as separate works. But when you distribute the same sections as part of a whole which is a work based on the Library, the distribution of the whole must be on the terms of this License, whose permissions for other licensees extend to the entire whole, and thus to each and every part regardless of who wrote it.

Thus, it is not the intent of this section to claim rights or contest your rights to work written entirely by you; rather, the intent is to exercise the right to control the distribution of derivative or collective works based on the Library.

In addition, mere aggregation of another work not based on the Library with the Library (or with a work based on the Library) on a volume of a storage or distribution medium does not bring the other work under the scope of this License.

3. You may opt to apply the terms of the ordinary GNU General Public License instead of this License to a given copy of the Library. To do this, you must alter all the notices that refer to this License, so that they refer to the ordinary GNU General Public License, version 2, instead of to this License. (If a newer version than version 2 of the ordinary GNU General Public License has appeared, then you can specify that version instead if you wish.) Do not make any other change in these notices.

Once this change is made in a given copy, it is irreversible for that copy, so the ordinary GNU General Public License applies to all subsequent copies and derivative works made from that copy.

This option is useful when you wish to copy part of the code of the Library into a program that is not a library.

4. You may copy and distribute the Library (or a portion or derivative of it, under Section 2) in object code or executable form under the terms of Sections 1 and 2 above provided that you accompany it with the complete corresponding machine-readable source code, which must be distributed under the terms of Sections 1 and 2 above on a medium customarily used for software interchange.

If distribution of object code is made by offering access to copy from a designated place, then offering equivalent access to copy the source code from the same place satisfies the requirement to distribute the source code, even though third parties are not compelled to copy the source along with the object code.

5. A program that contains no derivative of any portion of the Library, but is designed to work with the Library by being compiled or linked with it, is called a "work that uses the Library". Such a work, in isolation, is not a derivative work of the Library, and therefore falls outside the scope of this License.

However, linking a "work that uses the Library" with the Library creates an executable that is a derivative of the Library (because it contains portions of the Library), rather than a "work that uses the library". The executable is therefore covered by this License. Section 6 states terms for distribution of such executables.

When a "work that uses the Library" uses material from a header file that is part of the Library, the object code for the work may be a derivative work of the Library even though the source code is not. Whether this is true is especially significant if the work can be linked without the Library, or if the work is itself a library. The threshold for this to be true is not precisely defined by law.

If such an object file uses only numerical parameters, data structure layouts and accessors, and small macros and small inline functions (ten lines or less in length), then the use of the object file is unrestricted, regardless of whether it is legally a derivative work. (Executables containing this object code plus portions of the Library will still fall under Section 6.)

Otherwise, if the work is a derivative of the Library, you may distribute the object code for the work under the terms of Section 6. Any executables containing that work also fall under Section 6, whether or not they are linked directly with the Library itself.

6. As an exception to the Sections above, you may also combine or link a "work that uses the Library" with the Library to produce a work containing portions of the Library, and distribute that work under terms of your choice, provided that the terms permit modification of the work for the customer's own use and reverse engineering for debugging such modifications.

You must give prominent notice with each copy of the work that the Library is used in it and that the Library and its use are covered by this License. You must supply a copy of this License. If the work during execution displays copyright notices, you must include the copyright notice for the Library among them, as well as a reference directing the user to the copy of this License. Also, you must do one of these things:

     a) Accompany the work with the complete corresponding machine-readable source code for the Library including whatever changes were used in the work (which must be distributed under Sections 1 and 2 above); and, if the work is an executable linked with the Library, with the complete machine-readable "work that uses the Library", as object code and/or source code, so that the user can modify the Library and then relink to produce a modified executable containing the modified Library. (It is understood that the user who changes the contents of definitions files in the Library will not necessarily be able to recompile the application to use the modified definitions.)

     b) Use a suitable shared library mechanism for linking with the Library. A suitable mechanism is one that (1) uses at run time a copy of the library already present on the user's computer system, rather than copying library functions into the executable, and (2) will operate properly with a modified version of the library, if the user installs one, as long as the modified version is interface-compatible with the version that the work was made with.

     c) Accompany the work with a written offer, valid for at least three years, to give the same user the materials specified in Subsection 6a, above, for a charge no more than the cost of performing this distribution.

     d) If distribution of the work is made by offering access to copy from a designated place, offer equivalent access to copy the above specified materials from the same place.

     e) Verify that the user has already received a copy of these materials or that you have already sent this user a copy.

For an executable, the required form of the "work that uses the Library" must include any data and utility programs needed for reproducing the executable from it. However, as a special exception, the materials to be distributed need not include anything that is normally distributed (in either source or binary form) with the major components (compiler, kernel, and so on) of the operating system on which the executable runs, unless that component itself accompanies the executable.

It may happen that this requirement contradicts the license restrictions of other proprietary libraries that do not normally accompany the operating system. Such a contradiction means you cannot use both them and the Library together in an executable that you distribute.

7. You may place library facilities that are a work based on the Library side-by-side in a single library together with other library facilities not covered by this License, and distribute such a combined library, provided that the separate distribution of the work based on the Library and of the other library facilities is otherwise permitted, and provided that you do these two things:

     a) Accompany the combined library with a copy of the same work based on the Library, uncombined with any other library facilities. This must be distributed under the terms of the Sections above.

     b) Give prominent notice with the combined library of the fact that part of it is a work based on the Library, and explaining where to find the accompanying uncombined form of the same work.

8. You may not copy, modify, sublicense, link with, or distribute the Library except as expressly provided under this License. Any attempt otherwise to copy, modify, sublicense, link with, or distribute the Library is void, and will automatically terminate your rights under this License. However, parties who have received copies, or rights, from you under this License will not have their licenses terminated so long as such parties remain in full compliance.

9. You are not required to accept this License, since you have not signed it. However, nothing else grants you permission to modify or distribute the Library or its derivative works. These actions are prohibited by law if you do not accept this License. Therefore, by modifying or distributing the Library (or any work based on the Library), you indicate your acceptance of this License to do so, and all its terms and conditions for copying, distributing or modifying the Library or works based on it.

10. Each time you redistribute the Library (or any work based on the Library), the recipient automatically receives a license from the original licensor to copy, distribute, link with or modify the Library subject to these terms and conditions. You may not impose any further restrictions on the recipients' exercise of the rights granted herein. You are not responsible for enforcing compliance by third parties with this License.

11. If, as a consequence of a court judgment or allegation of patent infringement or for any other reason (not limited to patent issues), conditions are imposed on you (whether by court order, agreement or otherwise) that contradict the conditions of this License, they do not excuse you from the conditions of this License. If you cannot distribute so as to satisfy simultaneously your obligations under this License and any other pertinent obligations, then as a consequence you may not distribute the Library at all. For example, if a patent license would not permit royalty-free redistribution of the Library by all those who receive copies directly or indirectly through you, then the only way you could satisfy both it and this License would be to refrain entirely from distribution of the Library.

If any portion of this section is held invalid or unenforceable under any particular circumstance, the balance of the section is intended to apply, and the section as a whole is intended to apply in other circumstances.

It is not the purpose of this section to induce you to infringe any patents or other property right claims or to contest validity of any such claims; this section has the sole purpose of protecting the integrity of the free software distribution system which is implemented by public license practices. Many people have made generous contributions to the wide range of software distributed through that system in reliance on consistent application of that system; it is up to the author/donor to decide if he or she is willing to distribute software through any other system and a licensee cannot impose that choice.

This section is intended to make thoroughly clear what is believed to be a consequence of the rest of this License.

12. If the distribution and/or use of the Library is restricted in certain countries either by patents or by copyrighted interfaces, the original copyright holder who places the Library under this License may add an explicit geographical distribution limitation excluding those countries, so that distribution is permitted only in or among countries not thus excluded. In such case, this License incorporates the limitation as if written in the body of this License.

13. The Free Software Foundation may publish revised and/or new versions of the Lesser General Public License from time to time. Such new versions will be similar in spirit to the present version, but may differ in detail to address new problems or concerns.

Each version is given a distinguishing version number. If the Library specifies a version number of this License which applies to it and "any later version", you have the option of following the terms and conditions either of that version or of any later version published by the Free Software Foundation. If the Library does not specify a license version number, you may choose any version ever published by the Free Software Foundation.

14. If you wish to incorporate parts of the Library into other free programs whose distribution conditions are incompatible with these, write to the author to ask for permission. For software which is copyrighted by the Free Software Foundation, write to the Free Software Foundation; we sometimes make exceptions for this. Our decision will be guided by the two goals of preserving the free status of all derivatives of our free software and of promoting the sharing and reuse of software generally.

NO WARRANTY

15. BECAUSE THE LIBRARY IS LICENSED FREE OF CHARGE, THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE LIBRARY, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW. EXCEPT WHEN OTHERWISE STATED IN WRITING THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND/OR OTHER PARTIES PROVIDE THE LIBRARY "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE LIBRARY IS WITH YOU. SHOULD THE LIBRARY PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION.

16. IN NO EVENT UNLESS REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW OR AGREED TO IN WRITING WILL ANY COPYRIGHT HOLDER, OR ANY OTHER PARTY WHO MAY MODIFY AND/OR REDISTRIBUTE THE LIBRARY AS PERMITTED ABOVE, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR DAMAGES, INCLUDING ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE LIBRARY (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF DATA OR DATA BEING RENDERED INACCURATE OR LOSSES SUSTAINED BY YOU OR THIRD PARTIES OR A FAILURE OF THE LIBRARY TO OPERATE WITH ANY OTHER SOFTWARE), EVEN IF SUCH HOLDER OR OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

How to Apply These Terms to Your New Libraries

If you develop a new library, and you want it to be of the greatest possible use to the public, we recommend making it free software that everyone can redistribute and change. You can do so by permitting redistribution under these terms (or, alternatively, under the terms of the ordinary General Public License).

To apply these terms, attach the following notices to the library. It is safest to attach them to the start of each source file to most effectively convey the exclusion of warranty; and each file should have at least the "copyright" line and a pointer to where the full notice is found.

     one line to give the library's name and an idea of what it does.
     Copyright (C) year  name of author

     This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

     This library is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.

     You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301  USA Also add information on how to contact you by electronic and paper mail.

You should also get your employer (if you work as a programmer) or your school, if any, to sign a "copyright disclaimer" for the library, if necessary. Here is a sample; alter the names:

Yoyodyne, Inc., hereby disclaims all copyright interest in
the library `Frob' (a library for tweaking knobs) written
by James Random Hacker.

signature of Ty Coon, 1 April 1990
Ty Coon, President of Vice
That's all there is to it!</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576921">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/build3test.bat</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e964283e16aa501eb868ad84839f6814</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e09deb6c6553acd4b99011707a4dc03207f50486</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>70cab2c2a7c9b9eb65f080621ed8f57d3fa4d9b011727953436be21953be3995</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:packageVerificationCode>
              <spdx:PackageVerificationCode>
                <spdx:packageVerificationCodeValue>3668afb28a3ecb9e59dec57d2abfee94609d414c</spdx:packageVerificationCodeValue>
              </spdx:PackageVerificationCode>
            </spdx:packageVerificationCode>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576908">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/xls_read.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>efbd11a376b20f27b2bf4536a4f3cd3d88654c14</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7ffc036470f63d94a9f1148328688fff50dd1409ca4320b4cc673ff1ebea4118</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ccacbb18a5f1456c342a6ffcb51abedf</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576904">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/test.mdb</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>95631eb4a310dc3e122ad315630cfe4e45d1f25df43a06567c7f68ae01eb1664</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>6b5027b70afb4b5445a32ea401bf102a</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>cc2aae22414e4d74874701858e37882c591497d5</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
            <spdx:externalRef>
              <spdx:ExternalRef>
                <spdx:referenceLocator>pkg:generic/adodbapi@2.6.2.0?download_url=https://files.pythonhosted.org/packages/40/fc/914289fdaf33352ab3412fc1fdc96c4c902715601bc603859bc533b51f5c/adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip</spdx:referenceLocator>
                <spdx:referenceCategory rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#referenceCategory_packageManager"/>
                <spdx:referenceType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/references/purl"/>
              </spdx:ExternalRef>
            </spdx:externalRef>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576914">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/adodbapitest.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7f0d75f8d2259dbc450f7382a56d9b9b</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ed8a6aa354caf5c74cf679b0d71307d5cca70c041c3bca0203adc010584e422e</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8bfb9132ff8e5262e4f9a2e5890270dfc837bd9a</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 2002 Henrik Ekelund</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576930">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-See-file">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-See-file</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>See-file</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>This license means that you can get copyright or license information through a reference file.

one example below:
/* 
 * Copyright (C) 2007  Olli Salonen &amp;lt;oasalonen@gmail.com&amp;gt;
 * see btnx.c for detailed license information
 * 
 * revoco.c is under a different copyright. See that file for details.
 * 
*/</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/quick_reference.md</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>991fde316650096a9558d93a8084096f58be5148</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8610566ef5f4bf3ba2dadd1172709e59b9307eb6eb227c96c25989668b54a4ab</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>77c29c117967fc2dabbd5fbafc5bbd64</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576897">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/remote/remote.md</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>9da664af53db98355cd6ff2950882bbe4b4e22708ddf9a9588816a1fe1960b52</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>2204eac2d14bd702b1cc8a43870c2f9b</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c2a234c1c0e0fc02f8dcd348b8460a438dde4add</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:filesAnalyzed rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >true</spdx:filesAnalyzed>
            <spdx:name>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip</spdx:name>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576911">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/adodbapi.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>6345658473ecca2b58d2cc0fa03788a5</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>38fbd44b4e63e88ed7265ac010d3f2ba7d6103f5</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>5c03f1e2710ca5c455665e97cb091005719cb1ffd4092858891bac11ce7de5cb</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 2002 Henrik Ekelund, versions 2.1 and later by Vernon Cole</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576935">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/adodbapi.egg-info/SOURCES.txt</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e394ef9d313139e1fd4581e23553bab863d8be72</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>62a9c020ff080bd8650a9b3c36a4dc4383de98eccfa3f28fbacc357193a9f98c</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e6f2fde54a3ac8bc9b2b723119a938e4</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576918">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/is64bit.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f51cf16fb0d0903792cb528f76f17dedeb83bbc4</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>9a150fede9862b9317abc1d848825241a342b073d867cfe3e7ef9f76c199e665</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>5f49e5f1e95e7be995285b17d80ddab4</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576934">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/adodbapi.egg-info/top_level.txt</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>f9a91b4e4489e778a99fab3f8163e27346ff3ca803a51a5830b197bed0eec9ae</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>d57c6f399d680d6faa1a997d03d6ffb9</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>1a3d5c9f3d82cdf01655fcfbb433d5a5d4d02837</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576893">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-See-doc.OTHER">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-See-doc.OTHER</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>See-doc.OTHER</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>License by Nomos.</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/apibase.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>fe7cf484c61bbfadcb4b5f934b93d53524f71c542a9c3eb77c11283267557511</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>67bfaa538b89f5fbe03e0024c77d8246</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>d10217163adb28ba10250702d4868f991a60987a</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 2002 Henrik Ekelund, version 2.1 by Vernon Cole</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576896">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/remote/adodbapi_service.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>aaf884f49e93a6246447f933df1cb8541dac2c21</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>bbaf4f170f0d75e66624b443859f51f139a78fc946764355eb9dca66f11dc715</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>0e549087a697bafe24de4d4f48cad8fd</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:packageFileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip</spdx:packageFileName>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576919">
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/dbapi20.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>87ebaa231036fcdab2a59956ad8829816b82c37d51b91c78911c0b7d06a782c2</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>dd6fc2ecbc119090cfc14b37a2821ca9015295ec</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-Public-domain">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-Public-domain</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>Public domain software</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>Public domain</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                    <spdx:licenseComments>The information in the file is:
This software is Public Domain and may be used without restrictions.
Thus we concluded Public-domain as license of this file</spdx:licenseComments>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>cdc0f5915f886b585808d94b4daad6c6</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-Public-domain"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-scancode-public-domain">
                        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-scancode-public-domain</spdx:licenseId>
                        <spdx:name>Public Domain</spdx:name>
                        <spdx:extractedText>License by Scancode.</spdx:extractedText>
                      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
                    </spdx:licenseInfoInFile>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576898">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/remote/server.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e8051c1d83d894703b4ceec6de42d3c7</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>47606054cc029fc1b03fb291207ca53bbdfdad96</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>417d939c42556f19774f392360d4b02a5800af75e17faab585809b2cc478205b</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 2013 by Vernon Cole http://sourceforge.net/projects/adodbapi</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576909">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/remote_xls_read.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>6be6d2fffdfb6e3e077950f15e0f9e49c24be99c4248914624cc42ec8625d223</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>3dfe792e8ae0fe5099d12c8d14a9da61</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>0af7f5112e723e7ae5987d92c37491afacf4722e</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576906">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/db_print_simple.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>0e7e3718de1db2a689e7c5f99c72b84cee085c06</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e46248d4bf5111a88292094018a1bc9428a24dbc3d015e4be3832a3380eef6aa</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>e7dc9a8e9397cc5b02e952feaa102530</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576912">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/is64bit.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>d98d0dc86d646950dd456c64915d8679</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8c733910e51240284f5885a21a84f7e5d71eb555</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>46f240200f804fbbb8a0eed4e2dac94e315da74c88e45221700c29d7e76556c3</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576924">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-See-doc.OTHER"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/__init__.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c8f55068772bfab50be5bcb89fe90292</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>7f638099bb5644bc75d7db0368a570c8b53b7353</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>fd617cf9a8fdaa4fe2807dc1767ffe7b66b204e4ed077abd57417eaddf913c80</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>Copyright (C) 2002 Henrik Ekelund, version 2.1 by Vernon Cole</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:checksum>
              <spdx:Checksum>
                <spdx:checksumValue>54eb0e9b94f083212168078d1d155eccdd70c013</spdx:checksumValue>
                <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
              </spdx:Checksum>
            </spdx:checksum>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576915">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/tryconnection.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>4d2e1b1d2f59a2afa923da1f7c7de694ae53dcbc</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>2aa8476068fcc1b3ef7e2c2f6d69874497e9b7679b4ff44000dda251f6e1e53c</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>1f2713f46bf3ccff7458c313d9b8fbfa</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576923">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/test_adodbapi_dbapi20.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>968f7613e99c9be9657b71a6a153b1e2d735c469a51bac171e3c62f8f80a6cf8</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>c6e225b3fd63fa1009ed57d509f090f0</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>abaf5f9743b2a2067a98078a82c6817c92936c12</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576916">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/test/runtests.bat</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8bc01e8827583c612a44eec881edffc7bd4d1d88</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>ca4333d5a33c5def9f685dbdb40e2c19087b4dfb2f6ca2a0fa7845dfacbe1812</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>aa4bcdf966db48ba0d5021d499449c1f</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576907">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/examples/db_print.py</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>b6caf921117e5c1c3c66123f8ef21e360b6c642998b8ba4a35b182d66151ca29</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>8c3b6c49f044ebd8ad4f329722bce06f</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>6358f1ae83c0e0a6e83331c4943b8b7b6fe3a789</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576937">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL"/>
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.0-or-later"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/adodbapi.egg-info/PKG-INFO</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>633612916ad127a6248b44e239d78096a1f2ca30</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>41322095cf1f3e21c57d8b7d54ea569bb08f2f647ef633647f9868d5e364c213</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>fb59e4310a3b185cd94cce4ca1a403bf</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:relationship>
              <spdx:Relationship>
                <spdx:relationshipType rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#relationshipType_contains"/>
                <spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
                  <spdx:File rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#SPDXRef-item9576936">
                    <spdx:licenseInfoInFile rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:fileName>adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip/adodbapi-2.6.2.0/adodbapi.egg-info/dependency_links.txt</spdx:fileName>
                    <spdx:licenseConcluded rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#noassertion"/>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>68b329da9893e34099c7d8ad5cb9c940</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_md5"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>adc83b19e793491b1c6ea0fd8b46cd9f32e592fc</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha1"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:checksum>
                      <spdx:Checksum>
                        <spdx:checksumValue>01ba4719c80b6fe911b091a7c05124b64eeece964e09c058ef8f9805daca546b</spdx:checksumValue>
                        <spdx:algorithm rdf:resource="http://spdx.org/rdf/terms#checksumAlgorithm_sha256"/>
                      </spdx:Checksum>
                    </spdx:checksum>
                    <spdx:copyrightText>NOASSERTION</spdx:copyrightText>
                  </spdx:File>
                </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
              </spdx:Relationship>
            </spdx:relationship>
            <spdx:licenseComments>licenseInfoInFile determined by Scanners:
 - nomos ("4.4.0.51".1e52cb)
 - monk ("4.4.0.51".1e52cb)
 - ojo ("4.4.0.51".1e52cb)
- scancode ("4.4.0.51".1e52cb)</spdx:licenseComments>
          </spdx:Package>
        </spdx:relatedSpdxElement>
      </spdx:Relationship>
    </spdx:relationship>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL"/>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-scancode-public-domain"/>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo>
      <spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:about="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-CC0-1.0">
        <spdx:licenseId>LicenseRef-CC0-1.0</spdx:licenseId>
        <spdx:name>Creative Commons Zero v1.0 Universal</spdx:name>
        <spdx:extractedText>Creative Commons Legal Code

CC0 1.0 Universal

    CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE
    LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN
    ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS
    INFORMATION ON AN "AS-IS" BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES
    REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS
    PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM
    THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED
    HEREUNDER.

Statement of Purpose

The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer
exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator
and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an "owner") of an original work of
authorship and/or a database (each, a "Work").

Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for
the purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and
scientific works ("Commons") that the public can reliably and without fear
of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other
works, reuse and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever
and for any purposes, including without limitation commercial purposes.
These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free
culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific
works, or to gain reputation or greater distribution for their Work in
part through the use and efforts of others.

For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any
expectation of additional consideration or compensation, the person
associating CC0 with a Work (the "Affirmer"), to the extent that he or she
is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily
elects to apply CC0 to the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its
terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and Related Rights in the
Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.

1. Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be
protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights ("Copyright and
Related Rights"). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not
limited to, the following:

  i. the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display,
     communicate, and translate a Work;
 ii. moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
iii. publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person's image or
     likeness depicted in a Work;
 iv. rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work,
     subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(a), below;
  v. rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data
     in a Work;
 vi. database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the
     European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal
     protection of databases, and under any national implementation
     thereof, including any amended or successor version of such
     directive); and
vii. other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the
     world based on applicable law or treaty, and any national
     implementations thereof.

2. Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention
of, applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently,
irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of
Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and causes
of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as
future claims and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories
worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or
treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future
medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever,
including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional
purposes (the "Waiver"). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each
member of the public at large and to the detriment of Affirmer's heirs and
successors, fully intending that such Waiver shall not be subject to
revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other legal or
equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public
as contemplated by Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.

3. Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason
be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the
Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into
account Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the
extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected
person a royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive,
irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise Affirmer's Copyright and
Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the
maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future
time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number
of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without
limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the
"License"). The License shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was
applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of the License for any
reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such
partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder
of the License, and in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she
will not (i) exercise any of his or her remaining Copyright and Related
Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and causes of
action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer's
express Statement of Purpose.

4. Limitations and Disclaimers.

 a. No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned,
    surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.
 b. Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or
    warranties of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied,
    statutory or otherwise, including without limitation warranties of
    title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non
    infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or
    the present or absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to
    the greatest extent permissible under applicable law.
 c. Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons
    that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without
    limitation any person's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work.
    Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary
    consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the
    Work.
 d. Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a
    party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to
    this CC0 or use of the Work.</spdx:extractedText>
      </spdx:ExtractedLicensingInfo>
    </spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo>
    <spdx:name>/srv/fossology/repository/report</spdx:name>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-only"/>
    <spdx:creationInfo>
      <spdx:CreationInfo>
        <spdx:created>2024-10-18T20:25:43Z</spdx:created>
        <spdx:licenseListVersion>3.22</spdx:licenseListVersion>
        <rdfs:comment>This document was created using license information and a generator from Fossology.
It contains the license and copyright analysis of adodbapi 2.6.2.0
Please check "LicenseComments" for explanations of concluded licenses</rdfs:comment>
        <spdx:creator>Person: Kanzlei Jun on behalf of AUDI AG</spdx:creator>
        <spdx:creator>Tool: fossology-4.4.0.51</spdx:creator>
      </spdx:CreationInfo>
    </spdx:creationInfo>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-Public-domain"/>
    <spdx:dataLicense>
      <spdx:ListedLicense rdf:about="http://spdx.org/licenses/CC0-1.0">
        <spdx:name>Creative Commons Zero v1.0 Universal</spdx:name>
        <spdx:isFsfLibre rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
        >true</spdx:isFsfLibre>
        <rdfs:seeAlso>https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/legalcode</rdfs:seeAlso>
        <spdx:crossRef>
          <spdx:CrossRef>
            <spdx:isWayBackLink rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >false</spdx:isWayBackLink>
            <spdx:isValid rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >true</spdx:isValid>
            <spdx:isLive rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
            >true</spdx:isLive>
            <spdx:url>https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/legalcode</spdx:url>
            <spdx:order rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#int"
            >0</spdx:order>
            <spdx:timestamp>2025-07-01T14:58:05Z</spdx:timestamp>
            <spdx:match>true</spdx:match>
          </spdx:CrossRef>
        </spdx:crossRef>
        <spdx:isOsiApproved rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
        >false</spdx:isOsiApproved>
        <spdx:isDeprecatedLicenseId rdf:datatype="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#boolean"
        >false</spdx:isDeprecatedLicenseId>
        <spdx:licenseName>Creative Commons Zero v1.0 Universal</spdx:licenseName>
        <spdx:standardLicenseTemplate>&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt;Creative Commons&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt; Legal Code&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;

&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;
CC0 1.0 Universal

&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt; CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION ON AN "AS-IS" BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER.

&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;
Statement of Purpose

The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an "owner") of an original work of authorship and/or a database (each, a "Work").

Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for the purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and scientific works ("Commons") that the public can reliably and without fear of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other works, reuse and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever and for any purposes, including without limitation commercial purposes. These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific works, or to gain reputation or greater distribution for their Work in part through the use and efforts of others.

For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any expectation of additional consideration or compensation, the person associating CC0 with a Work (the "Affirmer"), to the extent that he or she is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily elects to apply CC0 to the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and Related Rights in the Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.

   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="1.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights ("Copyright and Related Rights"). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not limited to, the following:
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="i.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display, communicate, and translate a Work;
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="ii.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="iii.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person's image or likeness depicted in a Work;
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="iv.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work, subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(a), below;
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="v.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data in a Work;
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="vi.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal protection of databases, and under any national implementation thereof, including any amended or successor version of such directive); and
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="vii.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the world based on applicable law or treaty, and any national implementations thereof.
   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="2.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention of, applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently, irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and causes of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as future claims and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the "Waiver"). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each member of the public at large and to the detriment of Affirmer's heirs and successors, fully intending that such Waiver shall not be subject to revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other legal or equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public as contemplated by Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.
   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="3.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into account Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected person a royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive, irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the "License"). The License shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of the License for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder of the License, and in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she will not (i) exercise any of his or her remaining Copyright and Related Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and causes of action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.
   &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="4.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Limitations and Disclaimers.
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="a.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned, surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="b.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or warranties of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including without limitation warranties of title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or the present or absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to the greatest extent permissible under applicable law.
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="c.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without limitation any person's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work. Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the Work.
      &lt;&lt;var;name="bullet";original="d.";match=".{0,20}"&gt;&gt; Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to this CC0 or use of the Work.&lt;&lt;beginOptional&gt;&gt; &lt;&lt;var;name="upstreamLink";original="";match="For more information, please see &lt;http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/&gt;"&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;endOptional&gt;&gt;</spdx:standardLicenseTemplate>
        <spdx:licenseId>CC0-1.0</spdx:licenseId>
        <spdx:licenseTextHtml>
      &lt;div class="optional-license-text"&gt; 
         &lt;div class="optional-license-text"&gt; 
            &lt;p&gt;Creative Commons&lt;var class="optional-license-text"&gt;  Legal Code&lt;/var&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

         &lt;/div&gt;
         &lt;p&gt;CC0 1.0 Universal&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class="optional-license-text"&gt; 
         &lt;p&gt;CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS
         DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION
         ON AN &amp;quot;AS-IS&amp;quot; BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT
         OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM THE
         USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED HEREUNDER.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Statement of Purpose&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer exclusive Copyright and Related
         Rights (defined below) upon the creator and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an &amp;quot;owner&amp;quot;)
         of an original work of authorship and/or a database (each, a &amp;quot;Work&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for the purpose of contributing to a
         commons of creative, cultural and scientific works (&amp;quot;Commons&amp;quot;) that the public can reliably
         and without fear of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other works, reuse
         and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever and for any purposes, including without
         limitation commercial purposes. These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a
         free culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific works, or to gain
         reputation or greater distribution for their Work in part through the use and efforts of others.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any expectation of additional consideration
         or compensation, the person associating CC0 with a Work (the &amp;quot;Affirmer&amp;quot;), to the extent that
         he or she is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily elects to apply CC0 to
         the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and
         Related Rights in the Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul style="list-style:none"&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; 1.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
          Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be protected by copyright and
             related or neighboring rights (&amp;quot;Copyright and Related Rights&amp;quot;). Copyright and
             Related Rights include, but are not limited to, the following:
          
&lt;ul style="list-style:none"&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; i.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display, communicate, and translate a Work;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; ii.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; iii.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person&amp;apos;s image or likeness depicted in a Work;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; iv.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work, subject to the limitations
                 in paragraph 4(a), below;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; v.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data in a Work;
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; vi.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the European Parliament and
                 of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal protection of databases, and under any
                 national implementation thereof, including any amended or successor version of such
                 directive); and
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; vii.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the world based on applicable
                 law or treaty, and any national implementations thereof.
            &lt;/li&gt;
            
&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; 2.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
          Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention of, applicable law,
             Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently, irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons,
             and surrenders all of Affirmer&amp;apos;s Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and
             causes of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as future claims
             and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum
             duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any
             current or future medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever,
             including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the
             &amp;quot;Waiver&amp;quot;). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each member of the public at
             large and to the detriment of Affirmer&amp;apos;s heirs and successors, fully intending that such
             Waiver shall not be subject to revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other
             legal or equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public as
             contemplated by Affirmer&amp;apos;s express Statement of Purpose.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; 3.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
          Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason be judged legally invalid
             or ineffective under applicable law, then the Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent
             permitted taking into account Affirmer&amp;apos;s express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to
             the extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected person a
             royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive, irrevocable and
             unconditional license to exercise Affirmer&amp;apos;s Copyright and Related Rights in the Work (i)
             in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or
             treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any
             number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation
             commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the &amp;quot;License&amp;quot;). The License shall
             be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of
             the License for any reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such
             partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder of the License, and
             in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she will not (i) exercise any of his or her
             remaining Copyright and Related Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and
             causes of action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer&amp;apos;s express
             Statement of Purpose.
        &lt;/li&gt;
        
&lt;li&gt;
            &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; 4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
          Limitations and Disclaimers.
          
&lt;ul style="list-style:none"&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; a.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned, surrendered, licensed
                 or otherwise affected by this document.
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; b.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or warranties of any kind
                 concerning the Work, express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including without
                 limitation warranties of title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non
                 infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or the present or
                 absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to the greatest extent permissible
                 under applicable law.
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; c.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons that may apply to the
                 Work or any use thereof, including without limitation any person&amp;apos;s Copyright and
                 Related Rights in the Work. Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any
                 necessary consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the Work.
            &lt;/li&gt;
               
&lt;li&gt;
                  &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern .{0,20}"&gt; d.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
              Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a party to this document
                 and has no duty or obligation with respect to this CC0 or use of the Work.
            &lt;/li&gt;
            
&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/li&gt;
      
&lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;var class="optional-license-text"&gt; &lt;var class="replaceable-license-text"&gt;&lt;span title="can be replaced with the pattern For more information, please see &lt;http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/&gt;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/var&gt;&lt;/var&gt;
    </spdx:licenseTextHtml>
        <spdx:licenseText>Creative Commons Legal Code

CC0 1.0 Universal

    CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE
    LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS DOCUMENT DOES NOT CREATE AN
    ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS
    INFORMATION ON AN "AS-IS" BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES
    REGARDING THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS
    PROVIDED HEREUNDER, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM
    THE USE OF THIS DOCUMENT OR THE INFORMATION OR WORKS PROVIDED
    HEREUNDER.

Statement of Purpose

The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer
exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator
and subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an "owner") of an original work of
authorship and/or a database (each, a "Work").

Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for
the purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and
scientific works ("Commons") that the public can reliably and without fear
of later claims of infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other
works, reuse and redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever
and for any purposes, including without limitation commercial purposes.
These owners may contribute to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free
culture and the further production of creative, cultural and scientific
works, or to gain reputation or greater distribution for their Work in
part through the use and efforts of others.

For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any
expectation of additional consideration or compensation, the person
associating CC0 with a Work (the "Affirmer"), to the extent that he or she
is an owner of Copyright and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily
elects to apply CC0 to the Work and publicly distribute the Work under its
terms, with knowledge of his or her Copyright and Related Rights in the
Work and the meaning and intended legal effect of CC0 on those rights.

1. Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be
protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights ("Copyright and
Related Rights"). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not
limited to, the following:

  i. the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display,
     communicate, and translate a Work;
 ii. moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
iii. publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a person's image or
     likeness depicted in a Work;
 iv. rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work,
     subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(a), below;
  v. rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data
     in a Work;
 vi. database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the
     European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal
     protection of databases, and under any national implementation
     thereof, including any amended or successor version of such
     directive); and
vii. other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the
     world based on applicable law or treaty, and any national
     implementations thereof.

2. Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention
of, applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently,
irrevocably and unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of
Affirmer's Copyright and Related Rights and associated claims and causes
of action, whether now known or unknown (including existing as well as
future claims and causes of action), in the Work (i) in all territories
worldwide, (ii) for the maximum duration provided by applicable law or
treaty (including future time extensions), (iii) in any current or future
medium and for any number of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever,
including without limitation commercial, advertising or promotional
purposes (the "Waiver"). Affirmer makes the Waiver for the benefit of each
member of the public at large and to the detriment of Affirmer's heirs and
successors, fully intending that such Waiver shall not be subject to
revocation, rescission, cancellation, termination, or any other legal or
equitable action to disrupt the quiet enjoyment of the Work by the public
as contemplated by Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose.

3. Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason
be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the
Waiver shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into
account Affirmer's express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the
extent the Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected
person a royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive,
irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise Affirmer's Copyright and
Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the
maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future
time extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number
of copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without
limitation commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the
"License"). The License shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was
applied by Affirmer to the Work. Should any part of the License for any
reason be judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such
partial invalidity or ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder
of the License, and in such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she
will not (i) exercise any of his or her remaining Copyright and Related
Rights in the Work or (ii) assert any associated claims and causes of
action with respect to the Work, in either case contrary to Affirmer's
express Statement of Purpose.

4. Limitations and Disclaimers.

 a. No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned,
    surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.
 b. Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or
    warranties of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied,
    statutory or otherwise, including without limitation warranties of
    title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non
    infringement, or the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or
    the present or absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to
    the greatest extent permissible under applicable law.
 c. Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons
    that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without
    limitation any person's Copyright and Related Rights in the Work.
    Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary
    consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the
    Work.
 d. Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a
    party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to
    this CC0 or use of the Work.
</spdx:licenseText>
      </spdx:ListedLicense>
    </spdx:dataLicense>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.0-or-later"/>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-See-doc.OTHER"/>
    <spdx:specVersion>SPDX-2.3</spdx:specVersion>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-LGPL-2.1-or-later"/>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-License-of-GNU-Licenses"/>
    <spdx:hasExtractedLicensingInfo rdf:resource="http://fossy.osadl.org/repo/SPDX2TV_adodbapi-2.6.2.0.zip_1729283142.spdx#LicenseRef-See-file"/>
  </spdx:SpdxDocument>
</rdf:RDF>
